<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrea Rau, PhD</title>
    <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrea Rau, PhD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andreamrau.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PhD &#43; Postdoc supervision</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/advising/phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/advising/phd/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Smahane Chalabi (2021-2022, Postdoc): A diet x epigenetics study in pigs, GENE-SWitCH grant (with Elisabetta Giuffra and Sarah Djebali) Fanny Mollandin (2019-2022, PhD): Incorporating known functional annotations into Bayesian genomic prediction models (with Pascal Croiseau, co-funding from EU Horizon 2020 RIA grant GENE-SWitCH) Dr. Manuel Revilla Sanchez (2016, 3-month PhD Erasmus+ Learning Mobility): An integrative gene network analysis of the genetic determination of pig fatty acid composition (with Jordi Estelle and Yuliaxis Ramayo Caldas) Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A first post</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&#39;m the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.
Here I am: content/blog\spoonful-series\01-spoonful.md  To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}
My content section is: blog  My layout is: single-series   does this work?     or this?      Let&amp;rsquo;s start.
beginning     middle     end     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer-reviewed articles</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/articles/</guid>
      <description>Rau, A. (2021) Cooking up knowledge from big data using data science. Frontiers in Young Minds, 9:632923. 📄 🔄 🗣 🔗 💻
  Mollandin, F., Rau, A., and Croiseau, P. (2021) An evaluation of the predictive performance and mapping power of the BayesR model for genomic prediction. G3, jkab225. 📄 🔄 💻
  Sellem, E., Marthey, S., Rau, A., Jouneau, L., Bonnet, A., Le Danvic, C., Kiefer, H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R software packages</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/coding/packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/coding/packages/</guid>
      <description> rpl: Randomized pairwise likelihood method for complex statistical inferences, available at GitHub padma: Pathway deviation scores using multiple factor analysis, available at BioC maskmeans: Multi-view aggregation/splitting K-means clustering algorithm, available at GitHub coseq: Co-expression analysis of sequencing data, available at BioC ICAL: Model selection for model based clustering of annotated data, available at GitHub metaRNASeq: Meta-analysis of RNA-seq data, available at CRAN HTSDiff: Differential analysis for RNA-seq data, available at R-Forge HTSFilter: Filter for replicated high-throughput sequencing data, available at BioC HTSCluster: Clustering high-throughput sequencing data with Poisson mixture models, available at CRAN ebdbNet: Empirical Bayes estimation for dynamic Bayesian networks, available at CRAN  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A second post</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&#39;m the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.
Here I am: content/blog\spoonful-series\02-spoonful\index.md  To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}
My content section is: blog  My layout is: single-series  Images in this page bundle: /blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/sidebar-inverse.jpg   part 2!     does this work?      now for some very cool things     more     get ready!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiny apps</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/coding/shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/coding/shiny/</guid>
      <description> Regeneration Rosetta: An R/Shiny interactive web application to explore regeneration-associated gene expression and chromatin accessibility, available as a Shiny web app Edge in TCGA: An R/Shiny interactive web application for the exploration of drivers of gene expression in The Cancer Genome Atlas, available as a Shiny web app Invest Astuces: An R/Shiny interactive web application for financial and real estate loan simulations, available as a Shiny web app  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books, book chapters &amp; dissertations</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/books/</guid>
      <description>Duranthon, V., Araújo, S., Palma, M., Rau, A., Matzapetakis, M., and Almeida, A. (2021) Rabbit research in the post-genomic era: transcriptome, proteome, and metabolome analysis. In: The Genetics and Genomics of the Rabbit., Ed. L. Fontanesi.
  Rau, A. (2017) Statistical methods and software for the analysis of transcriptomic data. HDR thesis, Université d’Évry Val-d’Essonne. HAL  PDF  Slides 
  Martin-Magniette, M.-L., Maugis-Rabusseau, C. and Rau, A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master&#39;s interns &#43; short-term contract supervision</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/advising/masters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/advising/masters/</guid>
      <description> Maxime Guilleton (2021, CDD (6 months)): Bioinformatics research engineer, LIPOMEC grant (with Mylène Delosiere) Alexandre Asset (2021, L2 internship): Inference of co-expression networks from intervention transcriptomic data (with Florence Jaffrézic and Denis Laloë) Solène Pety (2021, M1 internship): Knowledge transfer using multivariate gene expression projections onto a large-scale reference database (with Catherine Giauffret) Raphaëlle Momal-Leisenring (2017, M2 internship): Integrative statistical analysis of multi-omics data Frédéric Jehl (2017, M2 internship): Impact of heat stress on liver and blood transcriptomes of laying hens (with Tatiana Zerjal) Babacar Ciss (2016, M2 internship): Constructing predictive models for ovine production data (with Eli Sellem, Allice) Audrey Hulot (2015, M1 internship): Incorporating a priori biological knowledge into gene network inference from observational and intervention gene expression data (with Florence Jaffrézic) Meriem Benabbas (2015, M1 internship): Identifying differentially expressed genes from RNA-seq data using mixture models Marc Teissier and Chaoyu Dong (2014, M1 STV/EM-ABG internship): Power to detect significantly differential gene expression using RNA-seq data Rémi Bancal (2012, M2 internship): Gene network estimation by adaptive knockout experiments (with Grégory Nuel and Florence Jaffrézic) Mélina Gallopin (2012, M2 internship): Gene network inference from RNA sequencing expression data (with Gilles Celeux and Florence Jaffrézic)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A third post</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&#39;m the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.
Here I am: content/blog\spoonful-series\03-spoonful\index.markdown  Here is my R Markdown source file: blog\spoonful-series\03-spoonful\index.Rmarkdown You&#39;ll want to edit this file, then re-knit to see the changes take effect in your site preview.
 To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}
My content section is: blog  My layout is: single-series  Images in this page bundle: /blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/featured-photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committee membership</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/advising/committees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/advising/committees/</guid>
      <description> Ambre Giguelay (2021, PhD evaluation committee member (rapportrice)) Leila Khajavi (2021, PhD evaluation committee member (rapportrice)) Thibault Poinsignon (2021-2023, PhD advisory committee member) Nicolas Jouvin (2021, PhD evaluation committee member (rapportrice)) Lucile Broséus (2021, PhD evaluation committee member (rapportrice)) Wilfried Heyse (2020-2022, PhD advisory committee member) Antoine Leduc (2019-2022, PhD advisory committee member) Alyssa Imbert (2018, PhD evaluation committee member (rapportrice)) Frédéric Jehl (2017-2020, PhD advisory committee member) Valentin Voillet (2016, PhD evaluation committee member) Gabriel Guillocheau (2015-2018, PhD advisory committee member)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preprints</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/preprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/preprints/</guid>
      <description>Rau, A., Passet, B., Castille, J., Asset, A., Lecardonnel, J., Moroldo, M., Jaffrézic, F., Laloë, D., Moazami-Goudarzi, K., and Vilotte, J.-L. (2021) Potential genetic robustness of Prnp and Sprn double knockout mouse embryos towards ShRNA-lentiviral inoculation&amp;hellip; Preprint  Code 
  Cazals, A., Rau, A., Estellé, J., Bruneau, N., Coville, J.-L., Menanteau, P., Rossignol, M.-N., Jardet, D., Bevilacqua, C., Bed&amp;rsquo;Hom, B., Velge, P., and Calenge, F. (2021) Comparative analysis of the caecal tonsil transcriptome in two hen lines experimentally infected with Salmonella Enteritidis&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Applications</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/project/applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/project/applications/</guid>
      <description>My research is strongly motivated by applications in human, animal, and plant genomics. I have made strong efforts to contribute analyses and develop methods that can provide useful solutions in these areas.
 Animal genomics applications     Plant genomics applications     Human genomics applications     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-omic data integration</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/project/integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/project/integration/</guid>
      <description> Related software     Related publications     Talks     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network inference</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/project/networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/project/networks/</guid>
      <description> Related software     Related publications     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RNA-seq co-expression</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/project/coexpression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/project/coexpression/</guid>
      <description> Related software:     Related publications:     Talks:     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up your social</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/social/</guid>
      <description>There are five places where you can choose to show social icons. Here is the tl;dr:
 site header (set in config.toml), site footer (set in config.toml),  homepage (set in content/_index.md),  about page in the sidebar (set in content/about/sidebar/index.md), and  contact page (set in content/form/contact.md).  Read on to learn how to set up your social icons, and how to show/hide them.
Configure social     Wherever you end up wanting to show your social icons, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to start by setting up the links in your site config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Style your site colors</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/color-themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/color-themes/</guid>
      <description>You can totally customize your site&amp;rsquo;s theme colors within minutes of creating a new site. Read on to find out how, and decide which of the three options meets your needs.
Use a color theme     Hugo Apéro includes 8 built-in color themes that work &amp;ldquo;out of the box.&amp;rdquo; This means you can use a color theme to quickly customize the look of your site without needing to write any CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Style your site typography</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/fonts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/fonts/</guid>
      <description>As with color themes, you can completely customize your site&amp;rsquo;s fonts within minutes of creating a new site. How you do it depends on how much control and customization you need.
Embedded fonts     Hugo Apéro includes 6 embedded fonts that work &amp;ldquo;out of the box.&amp;rdquo; We selected 3 serif and 3 sans-serif options that we thought looked good with this theme, in our humble opinions. All embedded fonts include real italics so you may emphasize to your heart&amp;rsquo;s content ❤️!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An evergreen post</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/evergreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/evergreen/</guid>
      <description>Rendering mathematical equations     Examples from the mathjax demo. But they work with katex as well.
Rmarkdown     In .Rmarkdown documents, you can use either
$a \ne 0$ to get inline math: \(a \ne 0\). There is no conflict with using dollar symbols regularly, because knitr automatically escapes freestanding dollar symbols.
And you can use
$x = {-b \pm \sqrt{b^2-4ac} \over 2a}.$$ to get a math paragraph:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A campfire</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/talk/campfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/talk/campfire/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to give this talk! Stay tuned for video and slides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using panelsets</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/seedling/</guid>
      <description>Courtesy of panelset.js by Garrick Aden-Buie, from his xaringanExtra package: https://pkg.garrickadenbuie.com/xaringanExtra/#/panelset
For example, this panelset:
Hello! 👋 hello
 Goodbye 💨 goodbye
  Was created by combining this theme&amp;rsquo;s panelset and panel shortcodes:
{{&amp;lt; panelset class=&amp;#34;greetings&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} {{&amp;lt; panel name=&amp;#34;Hello! :wave:&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} hello {{&amp;lt; /panel &amp;gt;}} {{&amp;lt; panel name=&amp;#34;Goodbye :dash:&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} goodbye {{&amp;lt; /panel &amp;gt;}} {{&amp;lt; /panelset &amp;gt;}} You could also revert to HTML as well. For example, this panelset:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A seedling</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/talk/second-seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:15:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/talk/second-seedling/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Rmarkdown post</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description> Air quality     with(airquality, boxplot(Temp ~ Month)) with(airquality, plot(Ozone ~ Temp)) mlev &amp;lt;- levels(with(airquality, as.factor(Month))) with(airquality, plot(Ozone ~ Temp, pch = as.numeric(mlev), col = mlev)) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A seedling</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/talk/seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 14:15:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/talk/seedling/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Grid Scaffold</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/css-grid-scaffold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/css-grid-scaffold/</guid>
      <description>“Grid is the very first CSS module created specifically to solve the layout problems we&amp;rsquo;ve all been hacking our way around for as long as we&amp;rsquo;ve been making websites.”     — Chris House, A Complete Guide to CSS Grid Layout 1
 Overview     Since I began building websites in Y2K, I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count how many times the phrase &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;there&amp;rsquo;s got to be a better way to do this&amp;rdquo; has passed my lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Built-in Contact Form</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/built-in-contact-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/blog/built-in-contact-form/</guid>
      <description>Formspree makes it easy to receive submissions from HTML forms on your static website.      Functional Form     This theme has a form-to-email feature built in, thanks to the simple Formspree integration. All you need to activate the form is a valid recipient email address saved in the front matter of the form (/content/forms/contact.md). Of course, the example shown below (your@email.here) must not be used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/contact/</guid>
      <description>** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above. See form.html in the layouts folder.
Formspree requires a (free) account and new form to be set up. The link is made on the final published url in the field: Restrict to Domain. It is possible to register up to 2 emails free and you can select which one you want the forms to go to within Formspree in the Settings tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typography Styles &amp; Element Examples</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 12:27:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/elements/</guid>
      <description>Font Sizes   A A A A A A A A   6rem
(96px) 5rem
(80px) 3rem
(48px) 2.25rem
(36px) 1.5rem
(24px) 1.25rem
(20px) 1rem
(16px) .875rem
(14px)     Type Samples Head&amp;shy;line Sub&amp;shy;head&amp;shy;line Level 1 Heading One page to rule them all...well, not really. This page displays sample typography and page elements to illustrate their style. Things like headings and paragraphs showing the beautiful type scale, form elements, tabular data, and image layouts just to name a few.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:
   Desirée De Leon 🦒 (designed 5 of the custom color themes, made illustrations for the workshop, and provided general aesthetic feedback along the way)
   Garrick Aden-Buie 🧙‍♀️ (debugged headroom.js and lent his panelset.js code to the theme)
   Allison Horst 🐕 (awesome illustrations of campfires, seedlings, and evergreens, as well as my R Markdown hedgehog mascot 🦔)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/license/</guid>
      <description>My blog posts are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
