<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on Andrea Rau, PhD</title>
    <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing on Andrea Rau, PhD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Peer-reviewed articles</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/articles/</guid>
      <description>Noël, A., Dumas, C., Rottier, E., Beslay, D., Costagliola, G., Ginies, C., Nicolè, F., Rau, A., Le Conte, Y., and Mondet, F. (2023) Volatolome of the honey bee (Apis mellifera) worker brood: from egg to emergence. PLoS ONE, In press.
  Mollandin, F., Gilbert, H., Croiseau, P., and Rau, A. (2022) Accounting for overlapping annotations in genomic prediction models of complex traits. BMC Bioinformatics, 23:65. 🔗📄🔄💻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books, book chapters &amp; dissertations</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/books/</guid>
      <description>Duranthon, V., Araújo, S., Palma, M., Rau, A., Matzapetakis, M., and Almeida, A. (2021) Rabbit research in the post-genomic era: transcriptome, proteome, and metabolome analysis. In: The Genetics and Genomics of the Rabbit, Ed. L. Fontanesi.
  Rau, A. (2017) Statistical methods and software for the analysis of transcriptomic data. HDR thesis, Université d’Évry Val-d’Essonne.📄🗣
  Martin-Magniette, M.-L., Maugis-Rabusseau, C. and Rau, A. (2017) Clustering of co-expressed genes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preprints, submitted articles, and technical reports</title>
      <link>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/preprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreamrau.netlify.app/collection/writing/preprints/</guid>
      <description>Delosière, M., Bernard, L., Hurtaud, C., Guilleton, M., Viala, D., Rau, A., Bonnet, M. and Cebo, C. (2023) Protein signatures of spontaneous lipolysis and lipoprotein lipase activity in milk. Journal of ProteomicsSubmitted.
  Duran Garzon, C., Chemin, C., Rau, A., Decaux, B., Sellier-Richard, H., Drouaud, J., Soubigou-Taconnat, L., Brunaud, V., Martin, M.-L., Palaffre, C., Rayon, C., Lourgant, K., Guénin, S. Gutierrez, L., Charcosset, A., Coursol, S., and Giauffret, C.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
